{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Concrete \u0026 Garage Floor Coating Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46357/":{"taskOID":46357,"originalTaskOID":46357,"setID":1254,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7048,"questionDisplayText":"Surface Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of concrete surface will the coating be applied to? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10569,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10570,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10571,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10572,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Warehouse floor","answerDisplayText":"Warehouse floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior surface","answerDisplayText":"Interior surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10574,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Exterior surface","answerDisplayText":"Exterior surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5901,"questionDisplayText":"Area of Coverage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How much surface area do you wish to have covered?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20230,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"100 sq ft - 400 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 sq ft - 400 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20231,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"400 sq ft - 800 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"400 sq ft - 800 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20232,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Greater than 800 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 800 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5902,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Coatings","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are there any existing coatings on the surface?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20233,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20235,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20234,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5900,"questionDisplayText":"Surface Condition","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the current condition of the surface?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20226,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Smooth","answerDisplayText":"Smooth","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20227,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rough","answerDisplayText":"Rough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20228,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Small fissures","answerDisplayText":"Small fissures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20229,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Large uneven crevices","answerDisplayText":"Large uneven crevices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7048,"questionDisplayText":"Surface Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of concrete surface will the coating be applied to? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10569,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10570,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10571,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10572,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Warehouse floor","answerDisplayText":"Warehouse floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior surface","answerDisplayText":"Interior surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10574,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Exterior surface","answerDisplayText":"Exterior surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10569,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Garage floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10570,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10571,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10572,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Warehouse floor","answerDisplayText":"Warehouse floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Interior surface","answerDisplayText":"Interior surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10574,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Exterior surface","answerDisplayText":"Exterior surface","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5901,"questionDisplayText":"Area of Coverage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How much surface area do you wish to have covered?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20230,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"100 sq ft - 400 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 sq ft - 400 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20231,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"400 sq ft - 800 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"400 sq ft - 800 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20232,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Greater than 800 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 800 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20230,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"100 sq ft - 400 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"100 sq ft - 400 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20231,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"400 sq ft - 800 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"400 sq ft - 800 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20232,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Greater than 800 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 800 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5902,"questionDisplayText":"Existing Coatings","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are there any existing coatings on the surface?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20233,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20235,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20234,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20233,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20235,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20234,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5900,"questionDisplayText":"Surface Condition","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the current condition of the surface?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20226,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Smooth","answerDisplayText":"Smooth","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20227,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rough","answerDisplayText":"Rough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20228,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Small fissures","answerDisplayText":"Small fissures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20229,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Large uneven crevices","answerDisplayText":"Large uneven crevices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20226,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Smooth","answerDisplayText":"Smooth","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20227,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Rough","answerDisplayText":"Rough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20228,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Small fissures","answerDisplayText":"Small fissures","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20229,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Large uneven crevices","answerDisplayText":"Large uneven crevices","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/46357/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46357,"taskName":"Concrete Floor Coating-Apply","taskDescription":"Coat Concrete Floors with Epoxy or Hybrid Polymer","xmTaskDescriptor":"Concrete \u0026 Garage Floor Coating Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":300,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"floor flooring smooth glossy gloss","textMessagingName":"Concrete_Floor_Coating","rolloverLongDesc":"Coat Concrete Floors with Epoxy or Hybrid Polymer for Decorative or Sealant purposes","rolloverShortDesc":"Epoxy or Hybrid Polymer coating applied to concrete floors","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to apply concrete epoxy or Hybrid Polymer floor coating.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Garage Floor Coating \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Concrete Floor Coating Contractors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":55,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Concrete Floor Coating - Apply","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Concrete Floor Coating-Apply","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Project","urlName":"Concrete-Floor-Coating-Apply","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete \u0026 Garage Floor Coating Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"floor, smooth, glossy, gloss,sealant, durability, durable, finish, Hybrid, seal, surface, garages, painting, coating, cement, concrete, epoxy","emcCategoryOid":-12036,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1254,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}